[{"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把玩具选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/圆珠笔.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/铅笔_3.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/T恤_3.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/polo_1.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/跳绳.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔3.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg"}], "unit": "件", "selectType": "toy", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[5, 7], [2]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-10"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把玩具选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/尺子.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/夹克.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/棒球.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔1.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔3.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/毽子.svg"}], "unit": "件", "selectType": "toy", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[5, 6], [2]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-10"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把玩具选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔2.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具枪手.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小熊_1.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/跳绳.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裤_1.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/网球拍1.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_2.svg"}], "unit": "件", "selectType": "toy", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 2, 4], [3]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-10"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把体育器材选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具飞机_1.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/T恤_3.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/尺子.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_1.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/跳绳.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/足球.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔1.svg"}], "unit": "件", "selectType": "sportEquipment", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[5, 6], [2]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-10"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把体育器材选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具机器人.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裤_1.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/网球.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/羽毛球.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_2.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/polo_2.svg"}], "unit": "件", "selectType": "sportEquipment", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[3, 4], [2]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-10"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把体育器材选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/橄榄球.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/polo_1.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/钢笔.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具手柄.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/圆珠笔.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔4.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具陀螺.svg"}], "unit": "件", "selectType": "sportEquipment", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[0], [1]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-10"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把体育器材选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具翻斗车_1.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/棒球棍.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/钢笔.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具娃娃.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/橄榄球.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/羽毛球.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/桌球.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/乒乓球拍.svg"}], "unit": "件", "selectType": "sportEquipment", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 4, 5, 6, 7], [5]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-10"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把玩具选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具铃铛.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/T恤_2.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/风车.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/网球.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_1.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/铅笔_3.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/长裤_1.svg"}], "unit": "件", "selectType": "toy", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[0, 2, 4], [3]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-10"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把体育器材选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/网球拍1.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/叠叠乐_1.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具小车_2.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/棒球.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/夹克.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/毽子.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/铅笔_3.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/长裤_1.svg"}], "unit": "件", "selectType": "sportEquipment", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[0, 3, 5], [3]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-10"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "把玩具选出来，再填一填。", "content": [{"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裤_1.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具积木.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/帽衫.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火车_1.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/衬衫.svg"}, {"type": "toy", "src": "v2/通用/玩具/玩具火箭.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/T恤_1.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/足球.svg"}], "unit": "件", "selectType": "toy", "type": "au-classify-fill-in", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[1, 3, 5], [3]], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-1-10"}]